Otsego County Conservation Association; Records apap158
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Solid Waste Management, 1987-1991; 3; 1 cubic foot
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Request for Proposals, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 35)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Tonnage Statistics, 1991-1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 36)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Transfer Station Fact Sheets, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 37)
  - Municipal Composting, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 38)
  - New York State, 1988; 1992-1993; 1995; 1998 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 39)
  - New York State Association for Reduction, Reuse, and Recycling, 1995; 1998-1999 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 40)
  - New York State Publications, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 41)
  - Oneida-Herkimer Solid Waste Authority, 1992-1993; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 42)
  - Onondaga County Resource Recovery Agency, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 43)
  - Other Counties, 1993; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 44)
  - Otsego County Solid Waste Committee, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 45)
  - Otsego County Solid Waste Coordinator, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 46)
  - Packaging Reduction, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 47)
  - Reclamation, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 48)
  - Recycling Investment Program, 1995; 1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 49)
  - Solid Waste Association of North America, 1995-1999; 2001 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 50)
  - Tires and Asphalt Paving, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 51)
  - Town of Root Anti-Landfill Legislation, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 52)
  - Toxic Waste, 1994; 1996; 1998; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 53)
  - User Fee, 1995; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 54)
  - Waste Reduction, Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 55)
  - Waste-to-Energy, 1991; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 56)
- Other Projects and Issues, 1969-2001; 4; 1.5 cubic ft.
  This series includes materials on OCCA projects not involving Otsego Lake or s olid waste management, as well as subject files on various conservation issues. Topics of particular interest include the Cherry Valley sewer project, the Glimmerglass Opera Theater shed project, Otsego 2000s lawsuit against the Otsego County Planning Board, the Leatherstocking Creek Stream Corridor project, and the Wal-Mart distribution center near Sharon Springs, New York, as well as subject files on agriculture and water quality issues.
  - Agriculture, News Clippings, 1994-2000; Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, Northeast Interstate Dairy Compact, News Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 2)
  - Canning Hoffman, Bonnie, Alexander Calder Conservation Award Nomination, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 3)
  - Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 4)
  - Center for Economic and Community Development, Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 5)
  - Cherry Valley Sewer Project, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 6)
  - Cherry Valley Sewer Project, Preliminary Engineer's Report, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 7)
  - Documentary, Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 8)
  - Electric Power, News Clippings, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 9)
  - Environmental Management Council, 1993-1995; 1998; 1999; Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 10)
  - Environmental Summit Meeting, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 11)
  - Events, Public, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 12)
  - Federation of Lake Associations, Waterworks, 1985 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 13)
  - Glimmerglass Opera Theater Shed, Environmental Impact Statement, Draft, 1985 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 14-15)
  - Green Party, News Clippings, Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 16)
  - Hartwick Composting Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 17)
  - Leatherstocking Creek Stream Corridor Project, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 18)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1983; 1985 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 19)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 208 Plan, Interim Reports, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 20)
  - New York State Government, Environmental and Other Issues, News Clippings, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 21)
  - News Clippings, 1970-1973; 1984-1989; 1994; 1998-2000; Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 22)
  - Non-Point Source Pollution, Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 23)
  - Otsego 2000, Town Planning Board Lawsuit, Appellant's Brief on Appeal, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 24)
  - Otsego 2000, Town Planning Board Lawsuit, Record on Appeal, Volume 1, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 25-27)
  - Otsego 2000, Town Planning Board Lawsuit, Record on Appeal, Volume 2, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 28)
  - Otsego Agricultural Conservation Program, Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 29)
  - Otsego County Board of Representatives, Citizens' Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 30)
  - Otsego County Conservation Association, News Clippings, 1969-1978 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 31)
  - Otsego County Environmental Management Council, 1970-1974; 1977-1979 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 32)
  - Otsego County Planning Department, Newsletter, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 33)
  - Otsego County Property Owners by Tax Parcel, 1985 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 34-36)
  - Press Releases, 1992; 1995-2000 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 37)
  - Public Service Commission, "Questions and Answers Explaining the Transmission Line Certification Process In New York State", 1982 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 38)
  - Soil Conservation, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 39)
  - Susquehanna River, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 40)
  - Three Mile Point Pavilion, Project Manual, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 41)
  - Wal-Mart, Distribution Center, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 1)
  - Water Pollution, 1970-1976 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 2)
  - Water Pollution, 1978-1981 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 3)
  - Water Pollution, News Clippings, 1970-1981 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 4)
  - Water Pollution, State Program for Control and Abatement, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 5)
  - Water Pollution and Drinking Water, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 6)
  - Water Pollution and Drinking Water, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 7)
  - Water Pollution and Drinking Water, News Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 8)
  - Water Problems, Southeastern New York, New York City, Catskills, 1980-1983 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 9)
  - Water Problems, Southeastern New York, New York City, Catskills, News Clippings, 1980-1983 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 10)
  - Wetlands, Undated (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 11)
  - Whaling, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Other Projects and Issues), Folder 12)